

# **GAURAV BORSE**

FRONTEND & BACKEND DEVELOPER || LEARNER

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

I am a Web Designer/Developer focused on crafting great web experiences. Designing and Coding have been my passion since the days I started working with computers but I found myself into web Design/Development since 2018. I enjoy creating beautifully designed, intuitive and functional websites..

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- jQuery
- JavaScript
- PHP Codelgniter
- Python Django
- C Programming
- C++
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD

# **CONTACT DETAILS:**

Mobile: +918329007426

Email: <u>gborse108@gmail.com</u>

Website:

Address: Mauli Lawns, Kamatwada

Nashik, 422009

# **COMPETENCIES**

- Good communication skills.
- Ability to Design/Develop modern, responsive Web Template.
- Skilled in all the major Languages required for Designing a modern Web Portal

## **CAREER HISTORY**

# **Full Stack Web Developer**

DDSIO, Nashik | Aug 2020 - Present

- Working as Junior Developer
- Managed Frontend as well as Backend
- Developed more than 15 Projects

#### NMC, Nashik

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

- We have Developed an NMC Sponsored website
  "Nashik Tourism" (<a href="https://tourism.nmc.gov.in/">https://tourism.nmc.gov.in/</a>). It is an Informative site for tourist who wants to travel in Nashik
- This site is completely Dynamic.

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

## **Government Polytechnic, Nashik**

Diploma in Computer Technology, 2020

- Attended from AUGUST 2017 to November 2020
- In the final semester, I have secured 93.33%.
- In these 3 years, I have learned different languages like PHP, Java, HTML, CSS, etc also studied DBMS and Data Structure

### **G.S High School, Amalner – School**

Class 10th, 2017

- I have secured 89.00% in the SSC board exam.

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS:**

- National Online Project
  Presentation Competition organized
  by Govt. Poly. Mumbai.
- Delivered workshop on Web Development at Govt. Poly. Nashik
- Explore ML Beginner Track workshop.